<W>UBISOFT PRIVACY POLICY</>

Last update:  10 July 2013

<W>WELCOME TO UBISOFT SERVICES.</> 

<W>PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY </>

Welcome to UBISOFT Services. UBISOFT is a world leader in the creation, publication and distribution of games and interactive content. UBISOFT is committed to offering the public innovative, high quality and safe games and content.
The purpose of this Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) is to emphasize our commitment to respect the privacy of the users of UBISOFT’s Internet sites and our games (“Users”). This Privacy Policy is an addendum to the Terms of Use of the UBISOFT sites and is governed by said Terms of Use, which are available at the following site: http://ubi.com/.
We collect information only in the context of our business activity and to enable us to respond to your requests, as required by the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act. You will never be asked to provide “sensitive” Personal Information such as your racial or ethnic origin, political, philosophical or religious opinions.
Information of a personal nature is defined as any information that could be used to directly or indirectly identify an individual (“Personal Information”). Information of a personal nature also includes any information that relates to an individual and could be used to identify that individual (“Personal Information” as described in greater detail below.
By registering, you are authorizing UBISOFT to process your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not accept this Policy, please do not use UBISOFT’s games on line or games that have online functions, Internet sites or online products and services (“Services”). 
IN WHAT CASES DOES UBISOFT COLLECT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
UBISOFT may collect and store your Personal Information when you perform certain procedures, which include but are not limited to the following:
-	(1) visit or play on one of its Services, 
-	(2) create a User Account,
-	(3) pay for a Service on line, 
-	(4) view advertising about the Services, 
-	(5) create User-generated content, 
-	(7) subscribe to automatic electronic message mailing lists (newsletter), 
-	(8) contact UBISOFT
-	(9) participate in a competition, 
-	(10) interact with other Users in a chat room or forum. 

<W>USE OF UBISOFT SITES</>

1.	Visiting UBISOFT sites

Connection information. Every time you connect to a Service, UBISOFT passively collects information, including but not limited to your IP address and your computer’s MAC address, console ID, connection date and time as well as information about your browser. This information is collected to, among other things, enable UBISOFT to control certain abusive behavior (as described below in “To Prevent Abuse”) on the part of users in violation of the Terms of Use. 

Browsing information. UBISOFT also collects information that will allow it to identify how you access the Internet sites, what pages you visit and how long you stay. UBISOFT may also use cookies. These cookies, the purpose of which is to improve the quality of your visit to the UBISOFT sites and to show you advertisements that match your interests on the pages of the UBISOFT sites or the UBISOFT games, are files that contain information UBISOFT can place on your computer’s hard drive to personalize your visit to the sites. You can accept or refuse these cookies by changing the settings in your Internet browser. 

2.	Registration on one of the Services 
Creating a User Account. Certain Services require the prior creation of a User Account. When you create your User Account you will be asked to provide the following information: username and password, email address, date of birth and country, without which you will not be able to create your User Account. You must first create a user Account if you wish to participate in a beta version test or download a demo version of a UBISOFT game.
3.	Subscription to automatic electronic message mailing lists 

When you create a User Account, you can give UBISOFT permission to send you newsletters concerning new products, services and promotions in the context of the Services. You can also give your permission for UBISOFT to disclose your Personal Information to companies and organizations that offer products and services that are likely to interest you.

4.	Contacts with UBISOFT

UBISOFT will use your last name, first name, email address and date of birth to respond to requests you may submit to UBISOFT Customer Service, to confirm the information and all transactions in your Account and to provide you with information about the Services (for example, if you forget your password or if changes are made to the Terms of Use).

5.	Participation in competitions, surveys or questionnaires organized by UBISOFT

UBISOFT will regularly offer you the opportunity to participate in surveys or questionnaires as well as in online game competitions. When you participate, you will be asked to provide your last name, first name, email address, date of birth, mailing address and country. In the context of your participation in competitions, this Personal Information will be used only in the context of your participation in competitions, for promotions relative to a specific product and to enable you to keep informed of new services and products. In the context of your participation in surveys or questionnaires, your Personal Information will be rendered anonymous to enable UBISOFT to compile statistics which will be used for internal purposes.

6.	Interactions in chat rooms and forums

When you participate and interact with other Users in a chat room or forum, UBISOFT will collect the content of your written and oral communications, the time and location of your activities and your online ID and IP address.

USE OF UBISOFT GAMES
7.	Registration at the time of the activation of a UBISOFT Game 

If you register to participate in UBISOFT games on a  console delivery service or system, your  console identifiers may be sent to UBISOFT so that UBISOFT can create a User Account for you. You must have an UBISOFT Account to use the UBISOFT games on line. The information sent to UBISOFT consists of your username and password, email address, date of birth and country.

8.	Creation of User-generated content

Certain Services make available tools and content to enable you to create and/or share original content. This User-generated content may be collected by UBISOFT and can be considered Personal Information by which you can be identified when you include your Personal Information or information relating to another person (for example, your name or image). UBISOFT cannot under any circumstances be held liable for any harmful consequences of the disclosure of User-generated content.

9.	Collection of game data during use of Services

During your Use of the Services, UBISOFT reserves the right to acquire, collect and record certain of your game data, for example the levels of play reached, rewards, playing time etc. to improve the Services and their quality and to adapt them to your specific interests and thereby improve your gaming experience.
ONLINE PAYMENTS

For certain Services, you have the ability to make purchases either on UBISOFT sites or directly within an UBISOFT game. 

In this context, you agree that UBISOFT may use outside service providers who will collect your Personal Information to make possible the proper operation of processing services for payments by credit card and the delivery of products, delivery of prizes or products offered in the context of promotions.

To pay for your purchase and for your payment to be processed you must provide your last name, first name, postal address, email address and country as well as your payment information, i.e. the number of your payment card, the name of the cardholder, the expiration date and the security codes.

We will store the details of your payment information as well as the details of your purchases from UBISOFT. The information on these transactions will be stored either by UBISOFT or by the outside service-provider if UBISOFT uses an outside service-provider. This information will be used for internal purposes as well as for the internal verification of accounts, accounting, compliance and for legal purposes in accordance with the policy for the storage of Personal Information set forth in this Privacy Policy.

You may be asked to provide the name of your telecommunications carrier, the model of your mobile telephone and a valid mobile telephone number so that you can make purchases directly from your mobile telephone.
HOW DOES UBISOFT PROTECT MY PERSONAL INFORMATION?
To protect your Personal Information, UBISOFT has implemented technical and administrative security measures to guarantee the security, integrity and confidentiality of your Personal Information. However, no method of data transmission via the Internet or electronic storage can guarantee 100% security. Consequently, UBISOFT cannot guarantee the absolute security of your Personal Information.
If your Accounts and your Personal Information are password-protected, it is your responsibility to ensure the confidentiality of your passwords. Never give this information to anyone. If you use a shared computer, do not forget to log off before leaving a Service.
WHY DOES UBISOFT USE MY PERSONAL INFORMATION?
1.	To manage your account 

UBISOFT uses your Personal Information to respond to your specific requests and purchase requests and to send you order confirmations and other information related to your Account. UBISOFT also uses your Personal Information to optimize and improve its Services. This information is used exclusively by UBISOFT and enables UBISOFT to better adapt its Services to the expectations of its Users.

2.	To prevent abuse

In case of obvious abuse of the Services on the part of Users, UBISOFT reserves the right to block certain User Accounts, certain IP addresses or certain console IDs provided by the manufacturers of licensed equipment. The IP address and the console ID can be used to identify you to enforce compliance with UBISOFT’S Terms of Use.

UBISOFT uses your date of birth or your age to control access to its forums and instant messaging services depending on the official classification. UBISOFT cannot monitor all of the chat rooms and makes no commitment in that regard. Nevertheless, UBISOFT reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to delete any content relative to your communications without notice. All the data collected in this manner can be used by UBISOFT to apply its Terms of Use, enforce the law and protect its rights, those of its subsidiaries and other users, as well as to ensure the safety of its employees and users. This information may be disclosed to any administrative or judicial authority having jurisdiction.

3.	Promotions and advertising

If you decided to receive emails from UBISOFT when you created your User Account, you will receive electronic messages relating to UBISOFT products and promotions. For that purpose UBISOFT will use the Personal Information you provided at the time of your registration. You may unsubscribe from this UBISOFT service at any time.

UBISOFT displays advertising on the pages of its Internet sites. These advertisements relate primarily to UBISOFT’S Services. UBISOFT may collect information by means of Cookies about the advertising links on which you or other users of your computer have clicked to show you advertisements that UBISOFT thinks match your demonstrated interests.

Certain Services may integrate a technology that shows a dynamic advertisement that is temporarily downloaded into an UBISOFT game. In these cases, UBISOFT records information originating from your console to guarantee that the correct advertising appears in the intended location in the game. The data recorded may include the IP and MAC addresses of the console, the location within the game, the duration of the advertisement, its size and viewing angle. This recorded information may be disclosed to third-party service providers and companies that deploy the technology used by this type of advertising.

The Services may contain links to third-party Internet sites outside UBISOFT, including but not limited to social networking sites. By clicking on a link to a third-party site, you acknowledge and agree that you are leaving the Services governed by this Privacy Policy and that UBISOFT does not control these third-party Internet sites. UBISOFT cannot guarantee that a third-party site will observe the same security and confidentiality practices as UBISOFT. UBISOFT cannot be held liable for any use that may be made of your Personal Information by these sites. We recommend that you verify the privacy policies of all the service providers you use.
HOW LONG DOES UBISOFT STORE MY PERSONAL INFORMATION?
UBISOFT will store your Personal Information only for the length of time strictly necessary for processing or for your use of the Service. Unless a different storage period is required by applicable laws and regulations, UBISOFT will store your Personal Information for a length of time strictly necessary for the uses explained in this Privacy Policy and in accordance with the requirements and restrictions of Article 4.5 of Schedule 1 to the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (L.C. 2000, Ch. 5) (the “Act”).
HOW DOES UBISOFT SHARE MY PERSONAL INFORMATION? 
UBISOFT may not disclose your Personal Information to a third party without your prior explicit permission.
1.	Sharing your information with other UBISOFT companies
Personal Information may be transmitted to other companies of the UBISOFT Group for the operation of the Services. Your Personal Information may be transferred to the registered office and subsidiaries of UBISOFT located in countries outside Canada, including but not limited to in Europe, the United States and China. The list of these subsidiaries is available online at 
http://www.ubisoftgroup.com/en-US/about_ubisoft/world_presence/world_presence.aspx.

Your data will be processed by teams working for UBISOFT or one of its subcontractors outside Canada and will be accessible to employees and agents of UBISOFT’s subsidiaries and/or subcontractors. Certain subsidiaries are located in countries that do not provide adequate protection within the meaning of Directive 95/46/EC of the European Parliament and of the Council dated 24 October 1995. Therefore UBISOFT has chosen to comply with internal corporate rules applicable to all of its worldwide subsidiaries pursuant to Article 26 (2) of this same Directive.

2.	Sharing of your Personal Information between UBISOFT and third-party companies

When you visit UBISOFT sites or use UBISOFT Games, outside service-providers may collect Personal Information in the name of and on behalf of UBISOFT. These third parties perform a service on behalf of UBISOFT to make possible the correct operation of services, delivery of products, delivery of prizes or products offered in the context of promotions, processing of payments by credit card and other services performed in the context of UBISOFT’S Services. Unless a third party asks you to accept its own confidentiality policy and terms of use, these third parties will share your Personal Information only with UBISOFT.

UBISOFT will never share Personal Information with third-party companies for marketing and/or commercial purposes without first having obtained your permission or that of a parent or legal guardian for children under the age of 13 (thirteen).

3.	Sharing with authorities 

UBISOFT may be required to disclose Personal Information to administrative or judicial authorities when such disclosure is necessary for the identification, interrogation or prosecution of any individual likely to cause harm to the rights of UBISOFT, any other User or a third party. Finally, UBISOFT may be required by law to disclose Personal Information, in which case it may not refuse.

4.	Sharing in the event of a merger

Third parties may access your Personal Information for purposes of negotiation for the purpose of the transfer in whole or in part of UBISOFT’s business activities. In that case, and for that purpose only, UBISOFT may permit the transfer of your Personal Information, including Data that identify a young child.
WHAT PRECAUTIONS ARE TAKEN TO PROTECT YOUNG CHILDREN? 
UBISOFT takes great care in protecting young children, and specifically in the security of visits by young children to UBISOFT’s Services and Games.

UBISOFT advises parents and legal guardians to exercise a certain degree of control when young children use the Internet.

1.	Online games for young children

Certain UBISOFT sites are specially designed for children and allow children over the age of 13 to create their own free Accounts, for which UBISOFT collets their username, password, date of birth, email address and country.

To allow children under the age of 13 to participate in online activities that require the collection of Personal Information, UBISOFT systematically requires the email address of a parent or legal guardian to obtain their consent prior to collecting Personal Information from children under the age of 13.

Parents or legal guardians can at any time create a “Parental Account” to manage the child’s Account by means of a special dedicated interface.

This personal information will be collected, used and disclosed as necessary exclusively for the purposes and reasons specified by UBISOFT at the time the information is collected. The parent or guardian of the young child must also give his or her consent by clicking on a button labeled “I accept”. In all cases, the personal information is stored by UBISOFT only for the length of time necessary for the purposes specified at the time the information is collected.

2.	Chat rooms or forums for minor children

When children under the age of 13 have access to a chat room or forum, their parents or legal guardians may select two instant messaging systems: (i) “normal chat”, which prevents the children from entering Personal Information to communicate with other Users and filters words and phrases defined as unacceptable to block content of a harmful or injurious nature; and (ii) “safe chat” which limits communications between young children to selections from a group of pre-selected phrases. “Report abuses” links are also made available to parents or guardians and to young children to help ensure the safety of UBISOFT’S sites, chat rooms and forums.

The consent of parents or legal guardians applies exclusively to the UBISOFT sites for which such consent has been given. In any case, UBISOFT reserves the right to restrict access by young children to all or part of a UBISOFT site.

UBISOFT shares Personal Information related to children under the age of 13 only when it has previously obtained consent from a parent or legal guardian.
WHAT ARE MY RIGHTS?
Under Article 4.9 of Schedule 1 of the Act, you have a right to access your Personal Information and, if necessary, the right to correct it as well as the right to challenge its dissemination on the UBISOFT site. 
You may contact UBISOFT Customer Service to exercise your right to challenge, access, correct or demand the removal of the information at the following address: http://support.ubi.com.
UBISOFT is required to respond to our request within a maximum period of 30 business days.
ABOUT THIS POLICY
UBISOFT reserves the right to amend this Policy at any time and to have you accept the new Policy following material amendments. We therefore recommend that you consult this Policy on a regular basis.
Your use of the Services after any amendment indicates your acceptance of said amendments. If you do not accept certain substantial amendments made to this Policy, you must cease using the Services.
QUESTIONS?
If you have any questions or wish to delete your User Account, please use the form available at the following address: http://support.ubi.com. 
