<W>UBISOFT PRIVACY STATEMENT </>
Your personal information.
Ubisoft collects your personal information when you register with us for our products or services, use our online store or otherwise contact us online.  We use this personal information to: provide you the products or services you have requested; create your user profile; to send you information about our products or services and your registration; when you agree, to send you marketing information; and to respond to your correspondence.  We do not share your information with anyone outside the Ubisoft group of companies.  For more information on how we use your personal information see our full Privacy Statement

Privacy Statement.
Ubisoft Entertainment Ltd, Ubisoft Entertainment SA, Ubisoft, Inc., Red Storm Entertainment, Inc., Blue Byte Software, Inc. are part of the same group of companies (together, "Ubisoft" or "we").  We respect the privacy rights of our online customers and are committed to protecting the personal information collected about you. We have adopted this Online Privacy Statement to guide how we collect, store, and use the information you provide us. By using the Ubisoft websites where this Privacy Statement is displayed (“Sites”), you signify your assent to the terms of the Privacy Statement. If you do not agree to this Privacy Statement, please do not use the Sites. We reserve the right to make changes in this policy, so please check back from time to time to ensure you are aware of any changes in our information collection practices. Your continued use of the Sites will signify your acceptance of these changes. This Privacy Statement was last updated on October 1st, 2012.

•	when does Ubisoft collect your personal information?
o	use a service?
o	register a product?
o	use Ubisoft’s online store?
•	what personal information does Ubisoft collect?
•	what happens if I refuse to provide my personal information? 
•	does Ubisoft use cookies, track IP addresses or use other passive means to collect my personal information? 
•	what about other websites?
•	how will my personal information be used and by whom? 
•	does Ubisoft share my personal information? 
•	can I choose how my personal information is used? 
•	how do I access my personal information? 
•	does Ubisoft collect personal information from children under 12? 
•	what safeguards does Ubisoft use to protect my personal information? 
•	how do I contact Ubisoft about my personal information? 
•	privacy statement and terms of use


When does Ubisoft collect your personal information?
Ubisoft collects your personal information at different times when you interact with our services, buy or products or otherwise contact us. Whatever the activity may be, we will only collect information to the extent deemed reasonably necessary to fulfil your requests and our legitimate business objectives.
o	use a service?
When you use a Site on which this Privacy Statement is made available or otherwise play Ubisoft's games or demos we will collect personal information about you as part of accessing a relevant service.
o	register a product?
If you wish to register your product online, you will be asked to provide us with the following personal information: first and last name, home address, telephone number and email address. We also ask you to enter information about the product you are registering such as the game's title and platform, and your reason for purchasing the product.
o	use Ubisoft’s online store?
In order to purchase goods and/or services from our online store, you will need to provide us with a valid credit card number and expiration date, in addition to name, mailing and billing addresses, phone number and e-mail address.
. 
What personal information Does Ubisoft Collect? 
Ubisoft only collects personal information from you on a voluntary basis. When you submit personal information to Ubisoft, it will usually take the form of: 
o	product registration
o	contest registration
o	demo or patch downloads
o	registration for game-specific event participation
o	shopping at our online store
o	Site registration;
o	customer service and technical support sessions; and/or 
The information we collect may include personal information such as your name, date of birth, e-mail address, phone number, fax number and home address. Visitors purchasing goods or services through our online store will need to provide a valid credit card number and expiration date, in addition to the credit card holder's name, mailing address, phone number and e-mail address. In addition, we may collect demographic information such as your age, gender, favourite styles of gaming and the systems you own or plan to buy. 
Ubisoft collects personal information via conventional Internet forms. For example, a new user to any of the Sites may be asked to register by providing his or her name, phone number, fax number, and home address. This information will then be associated with your e-mail account, so that you may identify yourself during future visits to each of the Sites. Ubisoft also stores and maintains personal information that you submit to us in an e-mail or that you post on our bulletin board. 
What happens if I refuse to provide my personal information? 
If you do not submit personal information when asked by Ubisoft, your refusal may limit our ability to process your online product registration, contest registration, purchase via our online store, or request for technical support. However, you do not need to provide personal information to Ubisoft in order to access and use the Sites. 
What about other websites?
In addition to the Sites, Ubisoft also owns several other domain names that may provide links to the Sites. We may from time to time also offer new websites that may or may not be Sites. Please note, however, that this policy applies only to the Sites on which this Privacy Statement is made available by Ubisoft and not to websites maintained by other companies or organizations to which we may provide links. Please note, however, that when you link to foreign sites or any other third party sites from our Sites, this Privacy Policy no longer applies. Ubisoft does not control the activities on those third party sites and  cannot and does not guarantee the security of any personal information disclosed on those third party sites. 
Does Ubisoft Use Cookies, Track IP Addresses or Use Other Passive Means to Collect Information? 
Ubisoft uses cookies on the Sites. A "cookie" is a small bit of record-keeping information that web sites often store on a user's computer. Cookies do not include people's names, e-mail addresses, or other information that is personally identifiable; they are typically used to quickly identify a user's computer and to "remember" things about the user's visit. For example, Ubisoft uses cookies to keep track of selected items in your shopping cart and to remember your login name and password. Any information collected this way is held only up until midnight of the same day, at which point, the information is deleted. You can disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent to your computer, although this may affect your ability to shop online. For more information about cookies, please see http://www.allaboutcookies.org. 
Ubisoft also keep tracks of Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for safety and security reasons. An IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer every time you log on to the Internet. 
The only other information passively collected by Ubisoft is in the form of logs - files that record web site activity, including how many "hits" a particular web page is getting (a.k.a. "click-through data"). This information is used in an aggregated form and not to identify specific use patterns of you or any individual.  These entries enable Ubisoft to assess overall site activity, track interest in advertised sales, and troubleshoot technical concerns. We also use the log file entries for our internal marketing and demographic studies, so we can constantly improve the referral services we provide you. 
Ubisoft may collect information regarding the user’s behaviour, and his/her use of Ubisoft’s demos and in-game data such as achievements, rankings, time played to better adapt our products and services to users’ interests and for a better quality of our services. 
Who is collecting my personal information and how will it be used? 
The information you submit to our Sites is collected and used by Ubisoft as set out above. In addition, Ubisoft may use the submitted information to send you advertising or promotional materials, including information about special rebates, promotional offers and other events of interest in accordance with your choices. We also use your personal information for our internal marketing and demographic studies, so we can constantly improve the products and services we provide you and to better meet your needs. 
From time to time, Ubisoft may employ third-party vendors, to collect personal information on Ubisoft's behalf. These third parties provide internal support to Ubisoft by operating some of the services we provide you including free email services and online product fulfilment. If we solicit third parties to collect personal information on our behalf, we require all such third parties to comply with and adhere to this Privacy Statement. When requesting these services, you may be asked to supply your name, billing and mailing addresses, email address, credit card number and valid expiration date. Although these third-party vendors, not Ubisoft, collect the personal information you provide when requesting such services, they do not share your personal information with third parties. In addition, Ubisoft has access to all information a third party collects on Ubisoft's behalf. 
If you use our Sites from outside Canada, please be aware that your personal information may be transferred to, stored in, and processed in Canada. The data protection and other laws of Canada have been recognised as providing an adequate level of protection for personal data by the European Commission. If you are transferring your personal data from the United Kingdom, please be assured that in processing any personal information in Canada, Ubisoft complies with these laws.  
With whom does Ubisoft share my personal information? 
Ubisoft may share your personal information among the Ubisoft group of companies.  This sharing enables us to provide you with information about products and services, which might interest you. To the extent that our corporate affiliates have access to your information, they will follow practices that are at least as restrictive as the practices described in this Privacy Statement.
From time to time, we may share your personal information with technical partners which help Ubisoft with the operation of the Services, including, without limitation, payment processing, and products delivery. To the extent that our technical partners have access to your information, they will follow practices that are at least as restrictive as the practices described in this Privacy Statement. 
From time to time, we are approached by companies and organizations that provide products or services that we believe may be of interest to you, and we may share your personal information with such third parties in accordance with your choices. We strive to limit use of the information you provide to those offers that we think you would appreciate receiving. If you do not wish to receive information from these third party partners, you can opt out at the time of information collection (i.e., when you fill out the product registration form). 
Should you decide to link your Ubisoft Account to your console manufacturer gaming account Ubisoft will only exchange information regarding your age, country, date of birth and email with such parties. No other personal information such as your credit card information or address will be exchanged with such parties. 
Can I choose how my personal information is used? 
If you do not want Ubisoft to send you communications about special rebates or promotional offers, you may opt-out from receiving these communications at the time your personal information is collected or by contacting us by:
o	fax at 01932 578001
o	email at webmaster@ubisoft.co.uk
o	post at Ubisoft Ltd, 1st Floor, Chertsey Gate East, London Street, Chertsey, Surrey, KT16 8AP, United Kingdom.
In addition, along with every communication sent to you, Ubisoft gives you the opportunity to discontinue receiving future communications. 
How do I access my personal information? 
If for any reason you wish to question, view, correct or delete the personal information collected about you by Ubisoft, please send an email to webmaster@ubisoft.co.uk or write to Ubisoft Ltd, 1st Floor, Chertsey Gate East, London Street, Chertsey, Surrey, KT16 8AP, United Kingdom. We will be happy to review, update or remove information as appropriate. However, we may still retain information in our files to resolve disputes, enforce our agreements, due to technical or legal requirements or matters related to security, integrity or operation of our Sites. 
Does Ubisoft Collect Personal Information from Children Under 12? 
Ubisoft encourages parents and guardians to spend time online with their children. We urge parents to instruct their children to never give out their real names, addresses or phone numbers, without permission, when using the Internet. We recognize a special obligation to protect personal information obtained from young children. Therefore, in order for children under 12 years old to register on any Site, , we require that the child provides the email address of a parent or guardian who will be contacted by Ubisoft in order to confirm, modify or refuse his or her child’s registration. Ubisoft reserves the right to request written proof of the parent or guardian’s authorization at any time. If the parent or guardian does not answer within 30 days of Ubisoft’s email, the child’s personal information will be deleted and his or her registration refused.”
What Safeguards Does Ubisoft Use to Protect My Personal Information? 
We take your privacy and the security of your personal information very seriously. We comply with the Data Protection Act 1998. To protect your personal information, Ubisoft maintains appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of the information you have provided. Our Sites have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Personal information collected by Ubisoft is stored in secure operating environments that are not available to the public (e.g., locked rooms). To prevent unauthorized electronic access to personal information, Ubisoft maintains information collected online behind a firewall-protected server and uses SSH encryption. 
In addition, we take reasonable steps to assure that third parties who collect personal information on our behalf provide sufficient protection of personal information in addition to requiring their compliance with this Privacy Statement at all times. 
How do I contact Ubisoft about my personal information?
Any questions or complaints or comments about this Privacy Statement or our use of your personal information, please contact our Privacy Statement  Administrator by:
•	phone at 01932 578000
•	email at webmaster@ubisoft.co.uk or, 
•	post at Ubisoft Ltd, 1st Floor, Chertsey Gate East, London Street, Chertsey, Surrey, KT16 8AP, United Kingdom. 

Privacy Statement and Terms of Use 
The terms of this Privacy Statement are incorporated into our Terms of Use. Please review our Terms of Use at: 
http://www.ubi.com/UK/Info/Info.aspx?tagname=TermsOfUse

